let exposure_trials = [
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Banana_Panana_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Ballerina</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Ballerina', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Ballerina', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '17', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Banana_Panana_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Ballerina_Pallerina_1_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Enlarge</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Balloon', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Enlarge', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '15', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Ballerina_Pallerina_1_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Balloon_Palloon_3_12.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Baloney</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Baloney', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Baloney', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '12', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Balloon_Palloon_3_12.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Baloney_Paloney_1_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Banana</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Banana', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Banana', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '10', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Baloney_Paloney_1_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Barely_Parely_1_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Barely</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Barely', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Barely', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '15', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Barely_Parely_1_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Barn_Parn_1_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Bark</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Barn', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Bark', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '20', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Barn_Parn_1_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Barren_Parren_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Barren</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Barren', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Barren', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '20', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Barren_Parren_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Belly_Pelly_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Berry</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Belly', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Berry', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '20', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Belly_Pelly_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Benign_Penign_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Benign</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Benign', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Benign', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '14', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Benign_Penign_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Biannual_Piannual_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Biannual</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Biannual', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Biannual', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '7', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Biannual_Piannual_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Billion_Pillion_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Bitter</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Billion', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Bitter', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '18', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Billion_Pillion_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Billionaire_Pillionaire_3_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Billionaire</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Billionaire', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Billionaire', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '8', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Billionaire_Pillionaire_3_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Blue_Plue_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Colleague</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Blue', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Colleague', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '17', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Blue_Plue_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Boil_Poil_1_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Boil</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Boil', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Boil', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '15', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Boil_Poil_1_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Boom_Poom_1_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Boom</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Boom', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Boom', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '15', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Boom_Poom_1_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Brain_Prain_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Brain</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Brain', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Brain', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '19', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Brain_Prain_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Brewery_Prewery_1_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Brewery</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Brewery', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Brewery', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '13', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Brewery_Prewery_1_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Brown_Prown_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Brown</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Brown', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Brown', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '11', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Brown_Prown_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Burial_Purial_1_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Burial</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Burial', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Burial', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '17', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Burial_Purial_1_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Burrow_Purrow_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Burrow</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Burrow', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Burrow', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '9', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Burrow_Purrow_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Barallel_Parallel_4_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Parallel</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Parallel', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Parallel', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Barallel_Parallel_4_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Barlor_Parlor_4_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Neutral</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Parlor', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Neutral', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Barlor_Parlor_4_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bawn_Pawn_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pawn</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Pawn', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pawn', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bawn_Pawn_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Beninsula_Peninsula_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Peninsula</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Peninsula', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Peninsula', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Beninsula_Peninsula_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Berform_Perform_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Perform</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Perform', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Perform', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Berform_Perform_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bioneer_Pioneer_4_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pillow</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Pioneer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pillow', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bioneer_Pioneer_4_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Blanner_Planner_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Planner</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Planner', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Planner', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Blanner_Planner_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Blea_Plea_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pick</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Plea', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pick', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Blea_Plea_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Blyer_Plyer_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Plyer</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Plyer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Plyer', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Blyer_Plyer_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bollen_Pollen_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pollen</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Pollen', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pollen', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bollen_Pollen_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bolymer_Polymer_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pottery</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Polymer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pottery', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bolymer_Polymer_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brayer_Prayer_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Prayer</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Prayer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Prayer', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brayer_Prayer_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Breliminary_Preliminary_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Temple</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Preliminary', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Temple', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Breliminary_Preliminary_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bremier_Premier_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Premier</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Premier', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Premier', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bremier_Premier_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brimal_Primal_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Primal</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Primal', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Primal', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brimal_Primal_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brime_Prime_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Prime</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Prime', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Prime', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brime_Prime_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brior_Prior_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Prior</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Prior', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Prior', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brior_Prior_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Browl_Prowl_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Prowl</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Prowl', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Prowl', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Browl_Prowl_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bry_Pry_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pry</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Pry', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pry', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bry_Pry_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bylon_Pylon_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pylon</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Pylon', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pylon', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bylon_Pylon_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Ally_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Agile</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Ally', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Agile', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Ally_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Area_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Arrogant</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Area', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Arrogant', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Area_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Arena_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Arena</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Arena', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Arena', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Arena_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Arrow_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Ambition</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Arrow', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Ambition', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Arrow_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Assume_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Assume</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Assume', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Assume', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Assume_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Aware_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Arrest</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Aware', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Arrest', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Aware_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Enemy_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Energy</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Enemy', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Energy', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Enemy_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Ensure_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Ensure</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Ensure', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Ensure', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Ensure_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Error_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Lonely</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Error', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Lonely', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Error_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Eye_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Verdict</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Eye', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Verdict', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Eye_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Failure_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Failure</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Failure', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Failure', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Failure_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Famous_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Loss</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Famous', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Loss', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Famous_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Flower_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Flourish</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Flower', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Flourish', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Flower_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Frame_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Frown</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Frame', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Frown', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Frame_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Funnel_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Deny</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Funnel', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Deny', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Funnel_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Hallway_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Harvest</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Hallway', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Harvest', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Hallway_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Hang_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Hang</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Hang', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Hang', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Hang_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Hill_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Hill</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Hill', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Hill', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Hill_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Hole_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Hurl</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Hole', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Hurl', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Hole_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Horn_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Heel</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Horn', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Heel', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Horn_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Jelly_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Jelly</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Jelly', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Jelly', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Jelly_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Jewel_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Tribute</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Jewel', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Tribute', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Jewel_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Lawyer_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Advice</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Lawyer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Advice', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Lawyer_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Layer_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Layer</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Layer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Layer', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Layer_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Learning_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Learning</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Learning', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Learning', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Learning_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Low_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Low</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Low', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Low', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Low_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Main_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Maid</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Main', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Maid', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Main_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Marine_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Mature</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Marine', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Mature', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Marine_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Memory_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Memory</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Memory', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Memory', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Memory_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Money_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Money</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Money', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Money', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Money_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Name_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Favor</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Name', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Favor', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Name_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Narrow_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Ankle</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Narrow', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Ankle', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Narrow_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Normal_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Nervous</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Normal', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Nervous', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Normal_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Nun_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Nun</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Nun', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Nun', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Nun_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Phenomenon_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Replace</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Phenomenon', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Replace', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Phenomenon_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Rally_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Knowledge</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Rally', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Knowledge', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Rally_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Range_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Spirit</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Range', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Spirit', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Range_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Reign_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Kettle</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Reign', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Kettle', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Reign_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Ring_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Retreat</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Ring', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Retreat', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Ring_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Roar_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Roar</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Roar', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Roar', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Roar_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Royal_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Refund</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Royal', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Refund', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Royal_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Ruin_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Ruin</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Ruin', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Ruin', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Ruin_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Rumor_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Rumor</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Rumor', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Rumor', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Rumor_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Runner_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">River</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Runner', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'River', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Runner_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Sailor_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Mine</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Sailor', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Mine', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Sailor_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Seal_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Chorus</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Seal', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Chorus', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Seal_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Shell_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Major</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Shell', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Major', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Shell_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Similar_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Seminar</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Similar', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Seminar', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Similar_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Soil_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Spoil</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Soil', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Spoil', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Soil_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Valley_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Greeting</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Valley', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Greeting', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Valley_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Vary_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Vary</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Vary', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Vary', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Vary_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Venue_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Vessel</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Venue', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Vessel', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Venue_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Volume_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Physical</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Volume', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Physical', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Volume_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Sewer_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Layout</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Sewer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Layout', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Sewer_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Swear_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Remark</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Swear', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Remark', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Swear_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 0, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Throne_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Throne</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Throne', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Throne', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Throne_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Banana_Panana_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Ballerina</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Ballerina', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Ballerina', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '17', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Banana_Panana_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Ballerina_Pallerina_1_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Enlarge</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Balloon', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Enlarge', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '15', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Ballerina_Pallerina_1_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Balloon_Palloon_3_12.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Baloney</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Baloney', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Baloney', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '12', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Balloon_Palloon_3_12.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Baloney_Paloney_1_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Banana</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Banana', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Banana', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '10', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Baloney_Paloney_1_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Barely_Parely_1_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Barely</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Barely', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Barely', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '15', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Barely_Parely_1_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Barn_Parn_1_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Bark</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Barn', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Bark', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '20', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Barn_Parn_1_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Barren_Parren_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Barren</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Barren', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Barren', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '20', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Barren_Parren_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Belly_Pelly_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Berry</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Belly', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Berry', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '20', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Belly_Pelly_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Benign_Penign_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Benign</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Benign', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Benign', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '14', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Benign_Penign_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Biannual_Piannual_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Biannual</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Biannual', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Biannual', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '7', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Biannual_Piannual_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Billion_Pillion_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Bitter</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Billion', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Bitter', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '18', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Billion_Pillion_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Billionaire_Pillionaire_3_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Billionaire</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Billionaire', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Billionaire', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '8', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Billionaire_Pillionaire_3_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Blue_Plue_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Colleague</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Blue', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Colleague', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '17', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Blue_Plue_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Boil_Poil_1_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Boil</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Boil', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Boil', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '15', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Boil_Poil_1_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Boom_Poom_1_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Boom</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Boom', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Boom', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '15', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Boom_Poom_1_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Brain_Prain_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Brain</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Brain', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Brain', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '19', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Brain_Prain_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Brewery_Prewery_1_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Brewery</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Brewery', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Brewery', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '13', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Brewery_Prewery_1_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Brown_Prown_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Brown</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Brown', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Brown', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '11', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Brown_Prown_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Burial_Purial_1_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Burial</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Burial', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Burial', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '17', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Burial_Purial_1_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Burrow_Purrow_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Burrow</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Burrow', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Burrow', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '9', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Burrow_Purrow_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Barallel_Parallel_4_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Parallel</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Parallel', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Parallel', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Barallel_Parallel_4_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Barlor_Parlor_4_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Neutral</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Parlor', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Neutral', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Barlor_Parlor_4_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bawn_Pawn_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pawn</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Pawn', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pawn', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bawn_Pawn_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Beninsula_Peninsula_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Peninsula</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Peninsula', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Peninsula', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Beninsula_Peninsula_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Berform_Perform_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Perform</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Perform', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Perform', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Berform_Perform_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bioneer_Pioneer_4_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pillow</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Pioneer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pillow', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bioneer_Pioneer_4_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Blanner_Planner_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Planner</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Planner', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Planner', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Blanner_Planner_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Blea_Plea_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pick</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Plea', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pick', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Blea_Plea_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Blyer_Plyer_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Plyer</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Plyer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Plyer', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Blyer_Plyer_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bollen_Pollen_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pollen</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Pollen', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pollen', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bollen_Pollen_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bolymer_Polymer_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pottery</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Polymer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pottery', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bolymer_Polymer_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brayer_Prayer_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Prayer</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Prayer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Prayer', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brayer_Prayer_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Breliminary_Preliminary_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Temple</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Preliminary', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Temple', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Breliminary_Preliminary_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bremier_Premier_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Premier</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Premier', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Premier', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bremier_Premier_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brimal_Primal_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Primal</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Primal', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Primal', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brimal_Primal_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brime_Prime_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Prime</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Prime', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Prime', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brime_Prime_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brior_Prior_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Prior</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Prior', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Prior', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brior_Prior_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Browl_Prowl_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Prowl</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Prowl', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Prowl', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Browl_Prowl_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bry_Pry_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pry</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Pry', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pry', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bry_Pry_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bylon_Pylon_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pylon</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Pylon', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pylon', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bylon_Pylon_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Ally_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Agile</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Ally', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Agile', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Ally_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Area_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Arrogant</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Area', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Arrogant', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Area_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Arena_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Arena</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Arena', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Arena', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Arena_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Arrow_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Ambition</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Arrow', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Ambition', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Arrow_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Assume_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Assume</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Assume', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Assume', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Assume_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Aware_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Arrest</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Aware', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Arrest', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Aware_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Enemy_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Energy</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Enemy', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Energy', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Enemy_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Ensure_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Ensure</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Ensure', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Ensure', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Ensure_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Error_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Lonely</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Error', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Lonely', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Error_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Eye_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Verdict</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Eye', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Verdict', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Eye_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Failure_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Failure</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Failure', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Failure', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Failure_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Famous_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Loss</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Famous', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Loss', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Famous_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Flower_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Flourish</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Flower', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Flourish', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Flower_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Frame_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Frown</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Frame', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Frown', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Frame_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Funnel_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Deny</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Funnel', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Deny', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Funnel_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Hallway_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Harvest</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Hallway', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Harvest', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Hallway_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Hang_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Hang</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Hang', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Hang', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Hang_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Hill_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Hill</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Hill', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Hill', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Hill_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Hole_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Hurl</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Hole', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Hurl', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Hole_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Horn_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Heel</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Horn', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Heel', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Horn_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Jelly_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Jelly</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Jelly', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Jelly', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Jelly_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Jewel_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Tribute</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Jewel', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Tribute', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Jewel_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Lawyer_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Advice</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Lawyer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Advice', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Lawyer_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Layer_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Layer</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Layer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Layer', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Layer_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Learning_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Learning</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Learning', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Learning', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Learning_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Low_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Low</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Low', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Low', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Low_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Main_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Maid</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Main', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Maid', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Main_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Marine_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Mature</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Marine', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Mature', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Marine_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Memory_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Memory</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Memory', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Memory', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Memory_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Money_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Money</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Money', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Money', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Money_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Name_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Favor</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Name', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Favor', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Name_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Narrow_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Ankle</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Narrow', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Ankle', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Narrow_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Normal_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Nervous</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Normal', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Nervous', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Normal_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Nun_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Nun</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Nun', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Nun', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Nun_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Phenomenon_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Replace</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Phenomenon', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Replace', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Phenomenon_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Rally_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Knowledge</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Rally', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Knowledge', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Rally_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Range_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Spirit</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Range', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Spirit', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Range_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Reign_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Kettle</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Reign', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Kettle', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Reign_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Ring_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Retreat</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Ring', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Retreat', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Ring_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Roar_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Roar</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Roar', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Roar', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Roar_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Royal_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Refund</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Royal', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Refund', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Royal_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Ruin_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Ruin</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Ruin', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Ruin', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Ruin_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Rumor_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Rumor</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Rumor', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Rumor', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Rumor_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Runner_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">River</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Runner', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'River', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Runner_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Sailor_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Mine</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Sailor', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Mine', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Sailor_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Seal_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Chorus</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Seal', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Chorus', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Seal_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Shell_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Major</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Shell', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Major', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Shell_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Similar_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Seminar</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Similar', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Seminar', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Similar_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Soil_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Spoil</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Soil', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Spoil', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Soil_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Valley_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Greeting</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Valley', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Greeting', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Valley_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Vary_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Vary</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Vary', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Vary', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Vary_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Venue_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Vessel</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Venue', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Vessel', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Venue_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Volume_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Physical</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Volume', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Physical', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Volume_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Sewer_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Layout</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Sewer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Layout', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Sewer_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Swear_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Remark</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Swear', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Remark', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Swear_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 2, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Throne_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Throne</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Throne', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Throne', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Throne_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Banana_Panana_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Ballerina</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Ballerina', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Ballerina', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '17', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Banana_Panana_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Ballerina_Pallerina_1_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Enlarge</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Balloon', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Enlarge', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '15', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Ballerina_Pallerina_1_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Balloon_Palloon_3_12.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Baloney</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Baloney', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Baloney', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '12', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Balloon_Palloon_3_12.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Baloney_Paloney_1_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Banana</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Banana', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Banana', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '10', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Baloney_Paloney_1_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Barely_Parely_1_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Barely</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Barely', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Barely', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '15', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Barely_Parely_1_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Barn_Parn_1_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Bark</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Barn', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Bark', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '20', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Barn_Parn_1_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Barren_Parren_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Barren</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Barren', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Barren', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '20', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Barren_Parren_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Belly_Pelly_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Berry</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Belly', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Berry', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '20', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Belly_Pelly_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Benign_Penign_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Benign</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Benign', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Benign', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '14', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Benign_Penign_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Biannual_Piannual_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Biannual</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Biannual', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Biannual', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '7', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Biannual_Piannual_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Billion_Pillion_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Bitter</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Billion', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Bitter', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '18', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Billion_Pillion_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Billionaire_Pillionaire_3_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Billionaire</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Billionaire', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Billionaire', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '8', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Billionaire_Pillionaire_3_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Blue_Plue_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Colleague</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Blue', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Colleague', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '17', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Blue_Plue_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Boil_Poil_1_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Boil</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Boil', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Boil', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '15', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Boil_Poil_1_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Boom_Poom_1_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Boom</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Boom', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Boom', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '15', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Boom_Poom_1_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Brain_Prain_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Brain</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Brain', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Brain', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '19', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Brain_Prain_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Brewery_Prewery_1_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Brewery</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Brewery', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Brewery', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '13', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Brewery_Prewery_1_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Brown_Prown_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Brown</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Brown', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Brown', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '11', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Brown_Prown_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Burial_Purial_1_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Burial</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Burial', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Burial', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '17', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Burial_Purial_1_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Burrow_Purrow_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Burrow</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Burrow', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Burrow', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '9', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Burrow_Purrow_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Barallel_Parallel_4_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Parallel</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Parallel', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Parallel', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Barallel_Parallel_4_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Barlor_Parlor_4_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Neutral</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Parlor', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Neutral', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Barlor_Parlor_4_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bawn_Pawn_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pawn</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Pawn', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pawn', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bawn_Pawn_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Beninsula_Peninsula_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Peninsula</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Peninsula', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Peninsula', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Beninsula_Peninsula_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Berform_Perform_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Perform</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Perform', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Perform', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Berform_Perform_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bioneer_Pioneer_4_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pillow</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Pioneer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pillow', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bioneer_Pioneer_4_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Blanner_Planner_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Planner</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Planner', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Planner', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Blanner_Planner_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Blea_Plea_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pick</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Plea', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pick', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Blea_Plea_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Blyer_Plyer_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Plyer</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Plyer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Plyer', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Blyer_Plyer_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bollen_Pollen_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pollen</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Pollen', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pollen', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bollen_Pollen_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bolymer_Polymer_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pottery</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Polymer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pottery', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bolymer_Polymer_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brayer_Prayer_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Prayer</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Prayer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Prayer', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brayer_Prayer_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Breliminary_Preliminary_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Temple</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Preliminary', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Temple', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Breliminary_Preliminary_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bremier_Premier_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Premier</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Premier', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Premier', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bremier_Premier_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brimal_Primal_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Primal</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Primal', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Primal', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brimal_Primal_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brime_Prime_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Prime</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Prime', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Prime', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brime_Prime_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brior_Prior_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Prior</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Prior', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Prior', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brior_Prior_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Browl_Prowl_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Prowl</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Prowl', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Prowl', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Browl_Prowl_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bry_Pry_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pry</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Pry', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pry', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bry_Pry_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bylon_Pylon_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pylon</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Pylon', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pylon', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bylon_Pylon_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Ally_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Agile</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Ally', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Agile', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Ally_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Area_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Arrogant</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Area', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Arrogant', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Area_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Arena_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Arena</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Arena', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Arena', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Arena_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Arrow_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Ambition</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Arrow', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Ambition', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Arrow_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Assume_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Assume</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Assume', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Assume', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Assume_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Aware_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Arrest</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Aware', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Arrest', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Aware_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Enemy_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Energy</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Enemy', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Energy', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Enemy_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Ensure_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Ensure</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Ensure', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Ensure', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Ensure_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Error_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Lonely</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Error', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Lonely', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Error_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Eye_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Verdict</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Eye', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Verdict', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Eye_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Failure_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Failure</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Failure', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Failure', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Failure_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Famous_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Loss</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Famous', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Loss', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Famous_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Flower_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Flourish</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Flower', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Flourish', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Flower_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Frame_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Frown</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Frame', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Frown', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Frame_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Funnel_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Deny</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Funnel', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Deny', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Funnel_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Hallway_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Harvest</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Hallway', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Harvest', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Hallway_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Hang_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Hang</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Hang', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Hang', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Hang_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Hill_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Hill</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Hill', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Hill', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Hill_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Hole_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Hurl</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Hole', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Hurl', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Hole_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Horn_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Heel</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Horn', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Heel', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Horn_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Jelly_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Jelly</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Jelly', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Jelly', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Jelly_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Jewel_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Tribute</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Jewel', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Tribute', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Jewel_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Lawyer_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Advice</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Lawyer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Advice', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Lawyer_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Layer_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Layer</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Layer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Layer', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Layer_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Learning_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Learning</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Learning', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Learning', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Learning_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Low_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Low</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Low', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Low', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Low_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Main_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Maid</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Main', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Maid', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Main_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Marine_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Mature</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Marine', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Mature', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Marine_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Memory_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Memory</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Memory', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Memory', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Memory_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Money_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Money</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Money', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Money', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Money_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Name_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Favor</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Name', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Favor', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Name_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Narrow_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Ankle</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Narrow', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Ankle', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Narrow_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Normal_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Nervous</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Normal', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Nervous', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Normal_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Nun_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Nun</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Nun', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Nun', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Nun_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Phenomenon_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Replace</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Phenomenon', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Replace', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Phenomenon_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Rally_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Knowledge</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Rally', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Knowledge', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Rally_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Range_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Spirit</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Range', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Spirit', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Range_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Reign_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Kettle</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Reign', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Kettle', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Reign_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Ring_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Retreat</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Ring', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Retreat', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Ring_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Roar_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Roar</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Roar', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Roar', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Roar_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Royal_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Refund</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Royal', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Refund', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Royal_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Ruin_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Ruin</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Ruin', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Ruin', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Ruin_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Rumor_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Rumor</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Rumor', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Rumor', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Rumor_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Runner_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">River</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Runner', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'River', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Runner_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Sailor_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Mine</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Sailor', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Mine', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Sailor_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Seal_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Chorus</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Seal', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Chorus', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Seal_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Shell_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Major</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Shell', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Major', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Shell_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Similar_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Seminar</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Similar', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Seminar', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Similar_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Soil_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Spoil</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Soil', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Spoil', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Soil_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Valley_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Greeting</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Valley', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Greeting', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Valley_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Vary_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Vary</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Vary', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Vary', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Vary_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Venue_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Vessel</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Venue', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Vessel', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Venue_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Volume_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Physical</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Volume', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Physical', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Volume_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Sewer_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Layout</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Sewer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Layout', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Sewer_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Swear_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Remark</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Swear', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Remark', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Swear_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 4, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Throne_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Throne</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Throne', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Throne', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Throne_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Banana_Panana_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Ballerina</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Ballerina', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Ballerina', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '17', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Banana_Panana_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Ballerina_Pallerina_1_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Enlarge</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Balloon', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Enlarge', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '15', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Ballerina_Pallerina_1_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Balloon_Palloon_3_12.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Baloney</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Baloney', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Baloney', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '12', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Balloon_Palloon_3_12.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Baloney_Paloney_1_10.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Banana</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Banana', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Banana', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '10', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Baloney_Paloney_1_10.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Barely_Parely_1_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Barely</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Barely', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Barely', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '15', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Barely_Parely_1_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Barn_Parn_1_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Bark</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Barn', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Bark', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '20', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Barn_Parn_1_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Barren_Parren_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Barren</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Barren', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Barren', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '20', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Barren_Parren_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Belly_Pelly_3_20.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Berry</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Belly', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Berry', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '20', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Belly_Pelly_3_20.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Benign_Penign_3_14.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Benign</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Benign', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Benign', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '14', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Benign_Penign_3_14.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Biannual_Piannual_3_07.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Biannual</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Biannual', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Biannual', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '7', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Biannual_Piannual_3_07.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Billion_Pillion_3_18.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Bitter</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Billion', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Bitter', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '18', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Billion_Pillion_3_18.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Billionaire_Pillionaire_3_08.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Billionaire</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Billionaire', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Billionaire', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '8', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Billionaire_Pillionaire_3_08.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Blue_Plue_3_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Colleague</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Blue', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Colleague', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '17', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Blue_Plue_3_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Boil_Poil_1_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Boil</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Boil', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Boil', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '15', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Boil_Poil_1_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Boom_Poom_1_15.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Boom</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Boom', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Boom', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '15', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Boom_Poom_1_15.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Brain_Prain_3_19.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Brain</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Brain', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Brain', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '19', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Brain_Prain_3_19.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Brewery_Prewery_1_13.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Brewery</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Brewery', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Brewery', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '13', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Brewery_Prewery_1_13.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Brown_Prown_3_11.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Brown</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Brown', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Brown', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '11', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Brown_Prown_3_11.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Burial_Purial_1_17.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Burial</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Burial', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Burial', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '17', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Burial_Purial_1_17.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Burrow_Purrow_3_09.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Burrow</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Burrow', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Burrow', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '9', path: 'audio/ambiguous_b/Burrow_Purrow_3_09.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Barallel_Parallel_4_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Parallel</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Parallel', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Parallel', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Barallel_Parallel_4_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Barlor_Parlor_4_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Neutral</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Parlor', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Neutral', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Barlor_Parlor_4_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bawn_Pawn_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pawn</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Pawn', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pawn', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bawn_Pawn_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Beninsula_Peninsula_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Peninsula</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Peninsula', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Peninsula', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Beninsula_Peninsula_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Berform_Perform_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Perform</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Perform', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Perform', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Berform_Perform_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bioneer_Pioneer_4_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pillow</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Pioneer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pillow', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bioneer_Pioneer_4_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Blanner_Planner_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Planner</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Planner', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Planner', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Blanner_Planner_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Blea_Plea_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pick</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Plea', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pick', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Blea_Plea_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Blyer_Plyer_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Plyer</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Plyer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Plyer', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Blyer_Plyer_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bollen_Pollen_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pollen</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Pollen', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pollen', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bollen_Pollen_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bolymer_Polymer_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pottery</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Polymer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pottery', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bolymer_Polymer_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brayer_Prayer_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Prayer</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Prayer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Prayer', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brayer_Prayer_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Breliminary_Preliminary_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Temple</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Preliminary', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Temple', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Breliminary_Preliminary_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bremier_Premier_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Premier</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Premier', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Premier', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bremier_Premier_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brimal_Primal_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Primal</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Primal', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Primal', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brimal_Primal_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brime_Prime_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Prime</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Prime', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Prime', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brime_Prime_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brior_Prior_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Prior</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Prior', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Prior', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brior_Prior_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Browl_Prowl_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Prowl</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Prowl', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Prowl', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Browl_Prowl_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bry_Pry_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pry</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Pry', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pry', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bry_Pry_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bylon_Pylon_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pylon</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Pylon', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pylon', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bylon_Pylon_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Ally_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Agile</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Ally', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Agile', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Ally_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Area_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Arrogant</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Area', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Arrogant', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Area_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Arena_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Arena</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Arena', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Arena', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Arena_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Arrow_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Ambition</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Arrow', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Ambition', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Arrow_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Assume_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Assume</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Assume', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Assume', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Assume_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Aware_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Arrest</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Aware', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Arrest', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Aware_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Enemy_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Energy</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Enemy', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Energy', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Enemy_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Ensure_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Ensure</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Ensure', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Ensure', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Ensure_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Error_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Lonely</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Error', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Lonely', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Error_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Eye_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Verdict</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Eye', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Verdict', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Eye_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Failure_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Failure</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Failure', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Failure', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Failure_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Famous_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Loss</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Famous', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Loss', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Famous_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Flower_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Flourish</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Flower', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Flourish', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Flower_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Frame_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Frown</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Frame', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Frown', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Frame_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Funnel_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Deny</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Funnel', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Deny', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Funnel_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Hallway_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Harvest</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Hallway', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Harvest', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Hallway_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Hang_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Hang</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Hang', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Hang', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Hang_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Hill_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Hill</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Hill', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Hill', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Hill_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Hole_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Hurl</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Hole', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Hurl', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Hole_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Horn_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Heel</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Horn', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Heel', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Horn_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Jelly_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Jelly</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Jelly', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Jelly', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Jelly_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Jewel_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Tribute</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Jewel', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Tribute', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Jewel_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Lawyer_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Advice</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Lawyer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Advice', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Lawyer_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Layer_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Layer</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Layer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Layer', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Layer_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Learning_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Learning</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Learning', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Learning', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Learning_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Low_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Low</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Low', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Low', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Low_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Main_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Maid</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Main', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Maid', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Main_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Marine_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Mature</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Marine', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Mature', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Marine_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Memory_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Memory</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Memory', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Memory', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Memory_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Money_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Money</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Money', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Money', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Money_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Name_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Favor</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Name', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Favor', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Name_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Narrow_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Ankle</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Narrow', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Ankle', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Narrow_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Normal_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Nervous</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Normal', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Nervous', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Normal_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Nun_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Nun</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Nun', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Nun', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Nun_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Phenomenon_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Replace</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Phenomenon', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Replace', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Phenomenon_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Rally_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Knowledge</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Rally', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Knowledge', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Rally_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Range_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Spirit</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Range', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Spirit', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Range_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Reign_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Kettle</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Reign', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Kettle', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Reign_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Ring_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Retreat</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Ring', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Retreat', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Ring_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Roar_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Roar</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Roar', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Roar', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Roar_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Royal_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Refund</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Royal', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Refund', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Royal_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Ruin_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Ruin</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Ruin', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Ruin', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Ruin_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Rumor_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Rumor</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Rumor', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Rumor', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Rumor_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Runner_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">River</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Runner', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'River', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Runner_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Sailor_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Mine</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Sailor', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Mine', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Sailor_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Seal_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Chorus</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Seal', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Chorus', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Seal_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Shell_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Major</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Shell', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Major', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Shell_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Similar_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Seminar</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Similar', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Seminar', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Similar_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Soil_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Spoil</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Soil', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Spoil', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Soil_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Valley_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Greeting</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Valley', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Greeting', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Valley_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Vary_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Vary</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Vary', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Vary', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Vary_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Venue_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Vessel</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Venue', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Vessel', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Venue_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Volume_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Physical</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Volume', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Physical', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Volume_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Sewer_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Layout</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Sewer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Layout', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Sewer_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Swear_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Remark</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Swear', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Remark', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Swear_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 6, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Throne_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Throne</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'b_group', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Throne', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Throne', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Throne_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Ballerina_Pallerina_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Ballerina</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Ballerina', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Ballerina', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Ballerina_Pallerina_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Balloon_Palloon_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Enlarge</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Balloon', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Enlarge', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Balloon_Palloon_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Baloney_Paloney_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Baloney</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Baloney', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Baloney', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Baloney_Paloney_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Banana_Panana_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Banana</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Banana', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Banana', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Banana_Panana_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Barely_Parely_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Barely</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Barely', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Barely', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Barely_Parely_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Barn_Parn_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Bark</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Barn', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Bark', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Barn_Parn_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Barren_Parren_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Barren</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Barren', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Barren', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Barren_Parren_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Belly_Pelly_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Berry</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Belly', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Berry', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Belly_Pelly_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Benign_Penign_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Benign</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Benign', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Benign', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Benign_Penign_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Biannual_Piannual_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Biannual</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Biannual', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Biannual', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Biannual_Piannual_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Billion_Pillion_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Bitter</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Billion', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Bitter', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Billion_Pillion_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Billionaire_Pillionaire_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Billionaire</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Billionaire', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Billionaire', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Billionaire_Pillionaire_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Blue_Plue_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Colleague</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Blue', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Colleague', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Blue_Plue_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Boil_Poil_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Boil</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Boil', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Boil', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Boil_Poil_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Boom_Poom_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Boom</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Boom', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Boom', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Boom_Poom_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Brain_Prain_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Brain</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Brain', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Brain', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Brain_Prain_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Brewery_Prewery_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Brewery</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Brewery', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Brewery', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Brewery_Prewery_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Brown_Prown_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Brown</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Brown', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Brown', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Brown_Prown_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Burial_Purial_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Burial</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Burial', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Burial', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Burial_Purial_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Burrow_Purrow_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Burrow</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Burrow', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Burrow', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Burrow_Purrow_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Barallel_Parallel_4_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Parallel</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Parallel', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Parallel', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Barallel_Parallel_4_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Barlor_Parlor_4_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Neutral</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Parlor', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Neutral', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Barlor_Parlor_4_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bawn_Pawn_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pawn</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Pawn', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pawn', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bawn_Pawn_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Beninsula_Peninsula_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Peninsula</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Peninsula', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Peninsula', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Beninsula_Peninsula_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Berform_Perform_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Perform</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Perform', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Perform', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Berform_Perform_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bioneer_Pioneer_4_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pillow</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Pioneer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pillow', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bioneer_Pioneer_4_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Blanner_Planner_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Planner</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Planner', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Planner', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Blanner_Planner_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Blea_Plea_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pick</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Plea', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pick', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Blea_Plea_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Blyer_Plyer_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Plyer</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Plyer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Plyer', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Blyer_Plyer_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bollen_Pollen_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pollen</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Pollen', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pollen', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bollen_Pollen_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bolymer_Polymer_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pottery</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Polymer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pottery', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bolymer_Polymer_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brayer_Prayer_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Prayer</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Prayer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Prayer', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brayer_Prayer_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Breliminary_Preliminary_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Temple</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Preliminary', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Temple', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Breliminary_Preliminary_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bremier_Premier_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Premier</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Premier', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Premier', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bremier_Premier_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brimal_Primal_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Primal</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Primal', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Primal', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brimal_Primal_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brime_Prime_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Prime</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Prime', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Prime', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brime_Prime_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brior_Prior_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Prior</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Prior', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Prior', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brior_Prior_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Browl_Prowl_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Prowl</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Prowl', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Prowl', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Browl_Prowl_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bry_Pry_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pry</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Pry', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pry', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bry_Pry_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bylon_Pylon_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pylon</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Pylon', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pylon', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bylon_Pylon_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Ally_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Agile</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Ally', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Agile', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Ally_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Area_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Arrogant</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Area', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Arrogant', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Area_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Arena_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Arena</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Arena', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Arena', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Arena_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Arrow_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Ambition</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Arrow', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Ambition', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Arrow_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Assume_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Assume</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Assume', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Assume', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Assume_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Aware_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Arrest</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Aware', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Arrest', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Aware_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Enemy_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Energy</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Enemy', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Energy', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Enemy_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Ensure_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Ensure</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Ensure', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Ensure', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Ensure_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Error_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Lonely</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Error', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Lonely', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Error_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Eye_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Verdict</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Eye', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Verdict', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Eye_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Failure_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Failure</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Failure', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Failure', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Failure_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Famous_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Loss</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Famous', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Loss', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Famous_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Flower_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Flourish</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Flower', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Flourish', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Flower_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Frame_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Frown</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Frame', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Frown', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Frame_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Funnel_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Deny</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Funnel', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Deny', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Funnel_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Hallway_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Harvest</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Hallway', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Harvest', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Hallway_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Hang_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Hang</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Hang', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Hang', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Hang_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Hill_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Hill</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Hill', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Hill', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Hill_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Hole_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Hurl</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Hole', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Hurl', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Hole_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Horn_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Heel</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Horn', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Heel', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Horn_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Jelly_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Jelly</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Jelly', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Jelly', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Jelly_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Jewel_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Tribute</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Jewel', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Tribute', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Jewel_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Lawyer_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Advice</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Lawyer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Advice', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Lawyer_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Layer_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Layer</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Layer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Layer', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Layer_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Learning_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Learning</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Learning', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Learning', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Learning_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Low_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Low</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Low', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Low', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Low_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Main_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Maid</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Main', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Maid', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Main_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Marine_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Mature</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Marine', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Mature', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Marine_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Memory_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Memory</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Memory', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Memory', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Memory_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Money_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Money</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Money', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Money', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Money_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Name_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Favor</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Name', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Favor', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Name_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Narrow_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Ankle</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Narrow', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Ankle', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Narrow_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Normal_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Nervous</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Normal', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Nervous', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Normal_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Nun_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Nun</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Nun', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Nun', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Nun_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Phenomenon_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Replace</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Phenomenon', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Replace', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Phenomenon_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Rally_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Knowledge</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Rally', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Knowledge', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Rally_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Range_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Spirit</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Range', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Spirit', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Range_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Reign_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Kettle</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Reign', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Kettle', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Reign_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Ring_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Retreat</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Ring', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Retreat', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Ring_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Roar_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Roar</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Roar', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Roar', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Roar_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Royal_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Refund</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Royal', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Refund', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Royal_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Ruin_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Ruin</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Ruin', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Ruin', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Ruin_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Rumor_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Rumor</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Rumor', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Rumor', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Rumor_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Runner_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">River</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Runner', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'River', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Runner_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Sailor_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Mine</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Sailor', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Mine', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Sailor_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Seal_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Chorus</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Seal', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Chorus', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Seal_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Shell_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Major</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Shell', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Major', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Shell_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Similar_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Seminar</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Similar', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Seminar', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Similar_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Soil_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Spoil</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Soil', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Spoil', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Soil_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Valley_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Greeting</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Valley', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Greeting', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Valley_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Vary_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Vary</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Vary', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Vary', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Vary_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Venue_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Vessel</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Venue', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Vessel', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Venue_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Volume_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Physical</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Volume', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Physical', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Volume_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Sewer_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Layout</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Sewer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Layout', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Sewer_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Swear_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Remark</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Swear', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Remark', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Swear_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 1, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Throne_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Throne</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Throne', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Throne', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Throne_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Ballerina_Pallerina_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Ballerina</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Ballerina', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Ballerina', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Ballerina_Pallerina_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Balloon_Palloon_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Enlarge</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Balloon', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Enlarge', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Balloon_Palloon_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Baloney_Paloney_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Baloney</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Baloney', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Baloney', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Baloney_Paloney_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Banana_Panana_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Banana</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Banana', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Banana', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Banana_Panana_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Barely_Parely_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Barely</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Barely', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Barely', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Barely_Parely_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Barn_Parn_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Bark</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Barn', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Bark', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Barn_Parn_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Barren_Parren_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Barren</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Barren', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Barren', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Barren_Parren_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Belly_Pelly_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Berry</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Belly', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Berry', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Belly_Pelly_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Benign_Penign_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Benign</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Benign', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Benign', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Benign_Penign_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Biannual_Piannual_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Biannual</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Biannual', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Biannual', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Biannual_Piannual_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Billion_Pillion_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Bitter</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Billion', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Bitter', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Billion_Pillion_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Billionaire_Pillionaire_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Billionaire</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Billionaire', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Billionaire', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Billionaire_Pillionaire_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Blue_Plue_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Colleague</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Blue', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Colleague', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Blue_Plue_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Boil_Poil_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Boil</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Boil', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Boil', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Boil_Poil_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Boom_Poom_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Boom</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Boom', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Boom', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Boom_Poom_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Brain_Prain_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Brain</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Brain', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Brain', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Brain_Prain_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Brewery_Prewery_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Brewery</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Brewery', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Brewery', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Brewery_Prewery_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Brown_Prown_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Brown</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Brown', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Brown', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Brown_Prown_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Burial_Purial_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Burial</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Burial', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Burial', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Burial_Purial_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Burrow_Purrow_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Burrow</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Burrow', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Burrow', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Burrow_Purrow_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Barallel_Parallel_4_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Parallel</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Parallel', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Parallel', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Barallel_Parallel_4_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Barlor_Parlor_4_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Neutral</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Parlor', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Neutral', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Barlor_Parlor_4_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bawn_Pawn_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pawn</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Pawn', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pawn', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bawn_Pawn_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Beninsula_Peninsula_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Peninsula</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Peninsula', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Peninsula', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Beninsula_Peninsula_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Berform_Perform_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Perform</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Perform', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Perform', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Berform_Perform_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bioneer_Pioneer_4_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pillow</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Pioneer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pillow', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bioneer_Pioneer_4_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Blanner_Planner_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Planner</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Planner', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Planner', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Blanner_Planner_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Blea_Plea_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pick</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Plea', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pick', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Blea_Plea_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Blyer_Plyer_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Plyer</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Plyer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Plyer', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Blyer_Plyer_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bollen_Pollen_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pollen</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Pollen', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pollen', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bollen_Pollen_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bolymer_Polymer_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pottery</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Polymer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pottery', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bolymer_Polymer_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brayer_Prayer_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Prayer</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Prayer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Prayer', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brayer_Prayer_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Breliminary_Preliminary_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Temple</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Preliminary', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Temple', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Breliminary_Preliminary_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bremier_Premier_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Premier</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Premier', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Premier', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bremier_Premier_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brimal_Primal_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Primal</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Primal', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Primal', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brimal_Primal_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brime_Prime_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Prime</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Prime', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Prime', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brime_Prime_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brior_Prior_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Prior</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Prior', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Prior', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brior_Prior_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Browl_Prowl_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Prowl</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Prowl', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Prowl', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Browl_Prowl_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bry_Pry_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pry</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Pry', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pry', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bry_Pry_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bylon_Pylon_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pylon</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Pylon', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pylon', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bylon_Pylon_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Ally_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Agile</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Ally', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Agile', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Ally_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Area_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Arrogant</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Area', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Arrogant', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Area_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Arena_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Arena</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Arena', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Arena', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Arena_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Arrow_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Ambition</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Arrow', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Ambition', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Arrow_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Assume_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Assume</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Assume', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Assume', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Assume_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Aware_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Arrest</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Aware', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Arrest', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Aware_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Enemy_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Energy</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Enemy', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Energy', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Enemy_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Ensure_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Ensure</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Ensure', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Ensure', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Ensure_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Error_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Lonely</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Error', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Lonely', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Error_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Eye_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Verdict</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Eye', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Verdict', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Eye_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Failure_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Failure</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Failure', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Failure', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Failure_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Famous_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Loss</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Famous', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Loss', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Famous_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Flower_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Flourish</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Flower', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Flourish', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Flower_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Frame_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Frown</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Frame', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Frown', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Frame_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Funnel_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Deny</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Funnel', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Deny', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Funnel_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Hallway_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Harvest</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Hallway', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Harvest', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Hallway_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Hang_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Hang</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Hang', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Hang', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Hang_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Hill_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Hill</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Hill', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Hill', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Hill_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Hole_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Hurl</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Hole', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Hurl', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Hole_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Horn_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Heel</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Horn', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Heel', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Horn_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Jelly_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Jelly</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Jelly', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Jelly', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Jelly_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Jewel_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Tribute</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Jewel', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Tribute', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Jewel_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Lawyer_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Advice</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Lawyer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Advice', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Lawyer_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Layer_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Layer</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Layer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Layer', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Layer_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Learning_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Learning</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Learning', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Learning', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Learning_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Low_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Low</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Low', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Low', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Low_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Main_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Maid</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Main', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Maid', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Main_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Marine_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Mature</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Marine', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Mature', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Marine_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Memory_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Memory</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Memory', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Memory', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Memory_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Money_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Money</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Money', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Money', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Money_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Name_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Favor</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Name', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Favor', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Name_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Narrow_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Ankle</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Narrow', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Ankle', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Narrow_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Normal_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Nervous</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Normal', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Nervous', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Normal_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Nun_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Nun</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Nun', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Nun', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Nun_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Phenomenon_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Replace</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Phenomenon', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Replace', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Phenomenon_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Rally_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Knowledge</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Rally', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Knowledge', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Rally_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Range_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Spirit</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Range', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Spirit', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Range_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Reign_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Kettle</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Reign', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Kettle', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Reign_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Ring_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Retreat</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Ring', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Retreat', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Ring_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Roar_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Roar</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Roar', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Roar', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Roar_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Royal_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Refund</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Royal', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Refund', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Royal_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Ruin_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Ruin</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Ruin', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Ruin', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Ruin_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Rumor_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Rumor</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Rumor', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Rumor', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Rumor_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Runner_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">River</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Runner', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'River', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Runner_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Sailor_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Mine</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Sailor', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Mine', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Sailor_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Seal_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Chorus</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Seal', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Chorus', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Seal_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Shell_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Major</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Shell', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Major', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Shell_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Similar_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Seminar</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Similar', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Seminar', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Similar_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Soil_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Spoil</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Soil', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Spoil', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Soil_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Valley_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Greeting</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Valley', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Greeting', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Valley_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Vary_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Vary</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Vary', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Vary', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Vary_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Venue_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Vessel</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Venue', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Vessel', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Venue_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Volume_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Physical</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Volume', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Physical', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Volume_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Sewer_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Layout</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Sewer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Layout', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Sewer_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Swear_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Remark</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Swear', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Remark', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Swear_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 3, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Throne_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Throne</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'DG', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Throne', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Throne', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Throne_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Ballerina_Pallerina_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Ballerina</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Ballerina', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Ballerina', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Ballerina_Pallerina_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Balloon_Palloon_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Enlarge</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Balloon', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Enlarge', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Balloon_Palloon_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Baloney_Paloney_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Baloney</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Baloney', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Baloney', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Baloney_Paloney_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Banana_Panana_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Banana</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Banana', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Banana', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Banana_Panana_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Barely_Parely_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Barely</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Barely', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Barely', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Barely_Parely_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Barn_Parn_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Bark</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Barn', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Bark', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Barn_Parn_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Barren_Parren_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Barren</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Barren', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Barren', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Barren_Parren_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Belly_Pelly_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Berry</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Belly', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Berry', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Belly_Pelly_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Benign_Penign_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Benign</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Benign', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Benign', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Benign_Penign_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Biannual_Piannual_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Biannual</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Biannual', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Biannual', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Biannual_Piannual_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Billion_Pillion_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Bitter</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Billion', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Bitter', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Billion_Pillion_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Billionaire_Pillionaire_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Billionaire</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Billionaire', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Billionaire', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Billionaire_Pillionaire_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Blue_Plue_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Colleague</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Blue', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Colleague', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Blue_Plue_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Boil_Poil_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Boil</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Boil', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Boil', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Boil_Poil_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Boom_Poom_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Boom</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Boom', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Boom', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Boom_Poom_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Brain_Prain_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Brain</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Brain', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Brain', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Brain_Prain_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Brewery_Prewery_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Brewery</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Brewery', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Brewery', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Brewery_Prewery_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Brown_Prown_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Brown</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Brown', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Brown', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Brown_Prown_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Burial_Purial_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Burial</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Burial', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Burial', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Burial_Purial_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Burrow_Purrow_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Burrow</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Burrow', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Burrow', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Burrow_Purrow_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Barallel_Parallel_4_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Parallel</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Parallel', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Parallel', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Barallel_Parallel_4_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Barlor_Parlor_4_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Neutral</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Parlor', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Neutral', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Barlor_Parlor_4_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bawn_Pawn_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pawn</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Pawn', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pawn', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bawn_Pawn_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Beninsula_Peninsula_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Peninsula</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Peninsula', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Peninsula', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Beninsula_Peninsula_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Berform_Perform_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Perform</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Perform', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Perform', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Berform_Perform_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bioneer_Pioneer_4_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pillow</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Pioneer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pillow', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bioneer_Pioneer_4_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Blanner_Planner_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Planner</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Planner', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Planner', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Blanner_Planner_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Blea_Plea_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pick</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Plea', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pick', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Blea_Plea_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Blyer_Plyer_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Plyer</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Plyer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Plyer', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Blyer_Plyer_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bollen_Pollen_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pollen</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Pollen', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pollen', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bollen_Pollen_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bolymer_Polymer_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pottery</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Polymer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pottery', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bolymer_Polymer_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brayer_Prayer_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Prayer</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Prayer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Prayer', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brayer_Prayer_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Breliminary_Preliminary_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Temple</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Preliminary', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Temple', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Breliminary_Preliminary_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bremier_Premier_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Premier</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Premier', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Premier', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bremier_Premier_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brimal_Primal_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Primal</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Primal', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Primal', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brimal_Primal_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brime_Prime_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Prime</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Prime', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Prime', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brime_Prime_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brior_Prior_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Prior</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Prior', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Prior', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brior_Prior_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Browl_Prowl_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Prowl</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Prowl', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Prowl', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Browl_Prowl_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bry_Pry_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pry</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Pry', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pry', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bry_Pry_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bylon_Pylon_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pylon</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Pylon', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pylon', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bylon_Pylon_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Ally_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Agile</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Ally', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Agile', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Ally_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Area_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Arrogant</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Area', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Arrogant', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Area_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Arena_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Arena</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Arena', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Arena', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Arena_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Arrow_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Ambition</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Arrow', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Ambition', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Arrow_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Assume_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Assume</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Assume', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Assume', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Assume_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Aware_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Arrest</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Aware', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Arrest', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Aware_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Enemy_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Energy</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Enemy', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Energy', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Enemy_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Ensure_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Ensure</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Ensure', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Ensure', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Ensure_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Error_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Lonely</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Error', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Lonely', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Error_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Eye_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Verdict</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Eye', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Verdict', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Eye_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Failure_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Failure</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Failure', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Failure', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Failure_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Famous_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Loss</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Famous', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Loss', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Famous_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Flower_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Flourish</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Flower', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Flourish', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Flower_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Frame_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Frown</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Frame', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Frown', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Frame_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Funnel_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Deny</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Funnel', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Deny', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Funnel_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Hallway_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Harvest</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Hallway', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Harvest', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Hallway_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Hang_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Hang</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Hang', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Hang', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Hang_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Hill_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Hill</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Hill', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Hill', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Hill_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Hole_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Hurl</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Hole', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Hurl', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Hole_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Horn_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Heel</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Horn', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Heel', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Horn_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Jelly_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Jelly</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Jelly', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Jelly', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Jelly_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Jewel_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Tribute</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Jewel', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Tribute', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Jewel_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Lawyer_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Advice</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Lawyer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Advice', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Lawyer_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Layer_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Layer</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Layer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Layer', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Layer_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Learning_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Learning</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Learning', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Learning', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Learning_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Low_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Low</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Low', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Low', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Low_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Main_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Maid</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Main', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Maid', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Main_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Marine_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Mature</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Marine', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Mature', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Marine_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Memory_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Memory</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Memory', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Memory', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Memory_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Money_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Money</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Money', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Money', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Money_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Name_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Favor</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Name', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Favor', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Name_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Narrow_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Ankle</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Narrow', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Ankle', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Narrow_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Normal_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Nervous</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Normal', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Nervous', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Normal_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Nun_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Nun</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Nun', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Nun', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Nun_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Phenomenon_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Replace</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Phenomenon', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Replace', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Phenomenon_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Rally_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Knowledge</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Rally', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Knowledge', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Rally_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Range_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Spirit</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Range', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Spirit', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Range_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Reign_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Kettle</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Reign', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Kettle', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Reign_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Ring_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Retreat</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Ring', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Retreat', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Ring_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Roar_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Roar</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Roar', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Roar', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Roar_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Royal_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Refund</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Royal', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Refund', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Royal_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Ruin_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Ruin</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Ruin', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Ruin', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Ruin_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Rumor_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Rumor</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Rumor', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Rumor', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Rumor_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Runner_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">River</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Runner', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'River', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Runner_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Sailor_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Mine</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Sailor', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Mine', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Sailor_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Seal_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Chorus</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Seal', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Chorus', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Seal_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Shell_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Major</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Shell', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Major', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Shell_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Similar_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Seminar</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Similar', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Seminar', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Similar_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Soil_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Spoil</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Soil', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Spoil', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Soil_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Valley_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Greeting</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Valley', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Greeting', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Valley_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Vary_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Vary</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Vary', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Vary', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Vary_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Venue_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Vessel</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Venue', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Vessel', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Venue_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Volume_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Physical</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Volume', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Physical', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Volume_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Sewer_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Layout</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Sewer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Layout', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Sewer_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Swear_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Remark</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Swear', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Remark', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Swear_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 5, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Throne_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Throne</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'LEFT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Throne', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Throne', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Throne_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Ballerina_Pallerina_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Ballerina</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Ballerina', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Ballerina', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Ballerina_Pallerina_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Balloon_Palloon_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Enlarge</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Balloon', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Enlarge', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Balloon_Palloon_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Baloney_Paloney_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Baloney</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Baloney', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Baloney', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Baloney_Paloney_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Banana_Panana_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Banana</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Banana', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Banana', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Banana_Panana_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Barely_Parely_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Barely</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Barely', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Barely', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Barely_Parely_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Barn_Parn_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Bark</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Barn', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Bark', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Barn_Parn_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Barren_Parren_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Barren</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Barren', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Barren', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Barren_Parren_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Belly_Pelly_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Berry</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Belly', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Berry', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Belly_Pelly_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Benign_Penign_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Benign</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Benign', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Benign', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Benign_Penign_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Biannual_Piannual_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Biannual</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Biannual', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Biannual', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Biannual_Piannual_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Billion_Pillion_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Bitter</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Billion', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Bitter', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Billion_Pillion_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Billionaire_Pillionaire_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Billionaire</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Billionaire', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Billionaire', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Billionaire_Pillionaire_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Blue_Plue_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Colleague</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Blue', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Colleague', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Blue_Plue_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Boil_Poil_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Boil</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Boil', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Boil', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Boil_Poil_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Boom_Poom_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Boom</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Boom', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Boom', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Boom_Poom_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Brain_Prain_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Brain</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Brain', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Brain', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Brain_Prain_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Brewery_Prewery_3_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Brewery</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Brewery', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Brewery', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Brewery_Prewery_3_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Brown_Prown_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Brown</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Brown', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Brown', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Brown_Prown_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Burial_Purial_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Burial</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Burial', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Burial', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Burial_Purial_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Burrow_Purrow_1_30.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Burrow</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Burrow', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Burrow', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '30', path: 'audio/unambiguous_b/Burrow_Purrow_1_30.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Barallel_Parallel_4_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Parallel</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Parallel', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Parallel', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Barallel_Parallel_4_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Barlor_Parlor_4_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Neutral</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Parlor', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Neutral', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Barlor_Parlor_4_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bawn_Pawn_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pawn</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Pawn', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pawn', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bawn_Pawn_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Beninsula_Peninsula_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Peninsula</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Peninsula', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Peninsula', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Beninsula_Peninsula_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Berform_Perform_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Perform</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Perform', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Perform', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Berform_Perform_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bioneer_Pioneer_4_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pillow</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Pioneer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pillow', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bioneer_Pioneer_4_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Blanner_Planner_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Planner</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Planner', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Planner', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Blanner_Planner_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Blea_Plea_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pick</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Plea', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pick', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Blea_Plea_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Blyer_Plyer_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Plyer</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Plyer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Plyer', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Blyer_Plyer_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bollen_Pollen_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pollen</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Pollen', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pollen', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bollen_Pollen_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bolymer_Polymer_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pottery</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Polymer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pottery', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bolymer_Polymer_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brayer_Prayer_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Prayer</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Prayer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Prayer', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brayer_Prayer_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Breliminary_Preliminary_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Temple</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Preliminary', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Temple', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Breliminary_Preliminary_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bremier_Premier_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Premier</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Premier', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Premier', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bremier_Premier_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brimal_Primal_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Primal</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Primal', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Primal', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brimal_Primal_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brime_Prime_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Prime</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Prime', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Prime', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brime_Prime_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brior_Prior_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Prior</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Prior', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Prior', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Brior_Prior_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Browl_Prowl_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Prowl</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Prowl', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Prowl', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Browl_Prowl_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bry_Pry_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pry</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Pry', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pry', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bry_Pry_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bylon_Pylon_2_00.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Pylon</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'crit_unamb', audio: 'Pylon', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Pylon', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: '0', path: 'audio/unambiguous_p/Bylon_Pylon_2_00.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Ally_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Agile</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Ally', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Agile', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Ally_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Area_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Arrogant</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Area', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Arrogant', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Area_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Arena_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Arena</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Arena', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Arena', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Arena_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Arrow_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Ambition</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Arrow', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Ambition', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Arrow_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Assume_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Assume</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Assume', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Assume', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Assume_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Aware_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Arrest</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Aware', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Arrest', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Aware_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Enemy_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Energy</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Enemy', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Energy', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Enemy_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Ensure_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Ensure</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Ensure', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Ensure', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Ensure_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Error_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Lonely</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Error', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Lonely', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Error_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Eye_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Verdict</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Eye', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Verdict', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Eye_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Failure_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Failure</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Failure', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Failure', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Failure_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Famous_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Loss</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Famous', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Loss', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Famous_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Flower_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Flourish</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Flower', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Flourish', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Flower_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Frame_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Frown</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Frame', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Frown', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Frame_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Funnel_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Deny</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Funnel', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Deny', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Funnel_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Hallway_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Harvest</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Hallway', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Harvest', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Hallway_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Hang_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Hang</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Hang', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Hang', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Hang_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Hill_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Hill</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Hill', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Hill', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Hill_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Hole_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Hurl</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Hole', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Hurl', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Hole_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Horn_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Heel</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Horn', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Heel', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Horn_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Jelly_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Jelly</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Jelly', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Jelly', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Jelly_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Jewel_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Tribute</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Jewel', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Tribute', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Jewel_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Lawyer_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Advice</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Lawyer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Advice', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Lawyer_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Layer_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Layer</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Layer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Layer', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Layer_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Learning_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Learning</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Learning', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Learning', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Learning_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Low_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Low</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Low', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Low', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Low_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Main_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Maid</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Main', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Maid', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Main_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Marine_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Mature</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Marine', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Mature', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Marine_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Memory_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Memory</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Memory', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Memory', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Memory_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Money_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Money</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Money', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Money', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Money_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Name_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Favor</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Name', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Favor', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Name_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Narrow_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Ankle</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Narrow', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Ankle', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Narrow_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Normal_2.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Nervous</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Normal', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Nervous', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Normal_2.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Nun_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Nun</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Nun', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Nun', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Nun_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Phenomenon_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Replace</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Phenomenon', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Replace', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Phenomenon_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Rally_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Knowledge</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Rally', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Knowledge', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Rally_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Range_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Spirit</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Range', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Spirit', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Range_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Reign_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Kettle</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Reign', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Kettle', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Reign_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Ring_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Retreat</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Ring', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Retreat', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Ring_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Roar_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Roar</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Roar', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Roar', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Roar_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Royal_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Refund</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Royal', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Refund', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Royal_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Ruin_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Ruin</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Ruin', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Ruin', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Ruin_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Rumor_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Rumor</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Rumor', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Rumor', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Rumor_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Runner_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">River</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Runner', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'River', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Runner_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Sailor_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Mine</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Sailor', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Mine', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Sailor_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Seal_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Chorus</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Seal', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Chorus', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Seal_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Shell_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Major</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Shell', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Major', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Shell_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Similar_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Seminar</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Similar', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Seminar', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Similar_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Soil_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Spoil</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Soil', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Spoil', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Soil_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Valley_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Greeting</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Valley', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Greeting', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Valley_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Vary_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Vary</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Vary', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Vary', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Vary_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Venue_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Vessel</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Venue', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Vessel', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Venue_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Volume_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Physical</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Volume', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Physical', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Volume_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Sewer_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Layout</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Sewer', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Layout', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Sewer_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Swear_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Remark</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'no', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Swear', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Remark', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Swear_1.wav' }}, 
{version: 7, type: 'audio-keyboard-response', stimulus: 'audio/filler/Throne_1.wav', choices: ['s', 'k'], prompt: '<div class="big-container"><p class="exposure-prompt">Throne</p><div class="yes-no"><div class="option-container"><p>DIFFERENT</p><p>Press S</p></div><div class="option-container"><p>SAME</p><p>Press K</p></div></div></div>', trial_duration: 4000, post_trial_gap: 1000, response_allowed_while_playing: false, data: { yes_side: 'RIGHT', block_order: 'GD', test_part: 'exposure', correct_response: 'yes', group: 'control', type: 'fill_word', audio: 'Throne', vowel: 'NA', visual_target: 'Throne', repetition: 'NA', normed_midpoint: 'NA', voiced_sel: 'NA', voiceless_sel: 'NA', match_sel: 'SAME', mismatch_sel: 'DIFFERENT', step: 'NA', path: 'audio/filler/Throne_1.wav' }},]